# **PANAGIOTIS** CHRISTAKAKIS

MSc STUDIES IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE & DATA ANALYTICS BSc IN APPLIED INFORMATICS





Ano Toumpa, Thessaloniki



+30



panoschristakakis@gmail.com



christakakis.github.io



/christakakis



/christakakis

# SKILLS

- Python, R. SQL, Neo4j
- Data Manipulation Visualization
- Machine Learning Algorithms
- **Experience with Computer Vision** and NLTK using TensorFlow
- **Data Structures**
- Supervised Unsupervised Learning
- Cooperative & Consistent

# LANGUAGES

**ECPE Proficiency C2** University of Michigan Dec 2015

#### INTERESTS

- Al and Medical Imaging
- Computer Vision
- Deep Learning / Transfer Learning
- Generative Adversarial Networks
- Autonomous Vehicles

# ADDITIONAL DETAILS

- Military Obligations Fulfilled
- Car License (Category: B)

# ABOUT

I'm currently studying for a Master's degree in Artificial Intelligence and Data Analytics at the University of Macedonia. In the last two semesters of my Bachelor's studies in Applied Informatics, I gained particular interest in the fields of Machine Learning and Data Analysis.

My goals? Interact in depth and enhance my prior experience with Machine Learning models, data analysis, statistical methods, and AI algorithms in general, while staying abreast of the emerging trends-techniques and their practical application in solving real-world challenges.

# EXPERIENCE

Research Assistant @ CERTH

Design and development of DL models & AI algorithms for the European Commission "HORIZON 2020 - PestNu" project

Kiosk Employee Family Business

2016 - 2022

2023 - present

# EDUCATION

**MSc in AI & Data Analytics** 



2022 - present

#### **BSc in Applied Informatics**



2018 - 2021

# REFERENCES

# **IOANNIS REFANIDIS**

Professor | UoM P: +30 2310 891.859 E:yrefanid@uom.edu.gr www.uom.gr/yrefanid

# **XINOGALOS STYLIANOS**

Professor | UoM P:+30 2310 891.895 E:stelios@uom.edu.gr www.uom.gr/stelios

# **EVANGELIDIS GEORGIOS**

Professor | UoM P: +30 2310 891.844 E:gevan@uom.edu.gr www.uom.gr/gevan

#### **MILOSSI MARIA**

Adjunct Lecturer | UoM E: mmilossi@uom.edu.gr www.uom.gr/mmilossi